Okay, I uploaded the five files
that Adam sent to me, and so,
and then I, uploaded a staff file,
and I put audit this staff file.
And so then it asked me, which chapters,
are we currently under? So I told it that we are currently under chapter
27, going for chapter 18 and so as you
can see Claude came back and said chapter 27 currently with
chapter 18 certification and process and then it explains what
exemption question once they know the level of care.
It asked me what our program level is currently and I said outpatient.
And so then it replied here,
explaining this a little bit and then it tell,
told me that it, it read all 16 of the files that were in
the folder and it explains kind of,
you know, exactly, entirely noted at the end,
not otherwise discussed and this was the person that we did.
And then gives the scopes,
the hire date, and it started to give me the findings.
Okay. So the findings here,
the first thing with the critical standard showed that this failed.
And so in the file, there was no annual,
review found, and what is, and then it tells you here what is required
that each facility or program will minimally form a review each calendar year
and the gap. So letting us know that it didn't exist.
The next thing was,
which is a critical standard again, where it is found.
I get it was fail because it said both because both
the 2025 training and sign-in sheets that's where it's located
and it had 13 training modules listed and
attested to but none of them, described as covering child abuse reporting.
And so it tells us exactly what was missing or what was required and
what was missing and where the gap was.
The next item, another critical standard that failed,
and where it was located. And again, it has to do with the,
the training. the next one, another unnecessary standard that
failed and it says exactly what's there and what was required
and it didn't see it listed.
The next one also fails same thing and it's saying that there
were no module trainings addressing co-occurring disorders,
letting us know again what was required and what wasn't here.
And the next one,
another critical standard is saying the status was unclear.
The whole file was there, but no privileging record found.
It wasn't a document and no first treatment service date appeared.
And so then again, And it's letting us know what is required,
that all staff shall be documented as privileged prior
to performing treatment services. So because it couldn't determine the sequencing,
or if it existed, it told us that it was unclear.
Same for this next critical standard for emergency procedures and safety
protocols. It's saying, you know, it observed,
it's telling you, telling us what was observed in the file,
what should be in the file, and then the gap.
another necessary standard, this was,
there was nothing, it observed that we did not have a module addressing age
developmentally appropriate care, which is required,
and it explains what the gap was,
you know, basically came down, it could not determine whether it was required,
let alone documented.
The next provision was,
this, this provision, or this standard here,
which is also a critical standard,
which governs all these sections,
and it does say that there were two documents existing for the same
training, and,
one was from 2025, another one from 2026,
shows both the staff signature and the date here,
over seven months after the calendar year closed,
so there's obviously an error there,
in service within 30 days of each employee's hire date and each calendar year
thereafter. So it has to be there, as well as the it did notice
that there were some conflicting com, completion dates.
let's see, here's another one, whole file,
no supervision log or entries found, so there's nothing in the file,
documents, supervision being provided to [EMPLOYEE NAME REDACTED],
and it does have [the employee's] job description and what it's supposed to do,
and, but it's still required that he provided and it shall address
the appropriateness of treatment and all the rest of these items again telling us
what the gap was. And on the things that
passed, now that we've seen everything that did not pass.
here, this was another, this was a critical standard,
and this one did pass because it was,
all staff who provide clinical services,
and so here is the information here showing that that was in the file.
the next one, whoops, was also,
another one that was another critical standard that did pass with the background
checks, showing that was there, all direct care staff shall be at least 18
years old. So that was there.
And then as you can see here,
it does list all of these. So module 11 through all of these did
pass. And so that does,
it did list those out one by one.
And then here's some things that were non-applicable.
So there was another critical standard,
and no non, intervention training documented.
We no longer have to do that for outpatient,
but inpatient does need that. then here's some other things that were not applicable.
It's the same exemptions, for chapter 27 as it is for chapter 18
and then here's some other things here that were not assessed and
then the summary so is filing so basically it is saying that
there were four findings, three critical,
it was these here, two necessary,
some nine passed, three not applicable, three not assessed,
five unclear. So it just gives us,
a rundown of everything here.
we went ahead and did the, the, I'm sorry,
the criminal history checks and everything here and yeah so this
was the employee file that we
used to have the auditor take care of so
thank you